<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>weekly on Alvan's Blog</title><link>/tags/weekly/</link><description>Recent content in weekly on Alvan's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 23:10:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/weekly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Status Update | 14 Nov 2021</title><link>/posts/2021/status-update-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 23:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2021/status-update-1/</guid><description>Introduction Hi, fellow reader!
So, recently I was consooming a bit more articles, from other programmers and designers, and suddenly I thought why I&amp;rsquo;m not writing my own thoughts? Basically, this is good idea, for example you get a chance to look back and remember things you have done. But I was a bit uhmm, how to say, kinda shy. Suddenly, my friend at themisir.com also said this is a good idea.</description><content>&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Hi, fellow reader!&lt;br>
So, recently I was consooming a bit more articles, from other programmers and designers, and suddenly I thought why I&amp;rsquo;m not writing my own thoughts? Basically, this is good idea, for example you get a chance to look back and remember things you have done. But I was a bit uhmm, how to say, kinda shy. Suddenly, my friend at &lt;a href="https://themisir.com">themisir.com&lt;/a> also said this is a good idea. So, this is me, Alvan, doing it :D&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="what-was-i-up-to">What was I up to?&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Recently my life got a massive DLC and there are some interesting things in it. Let&amp;rsquo;s break that into the pieces.&lt;br>
Basically, these are:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>New remote full-time job&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A startup project&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Another startup, where I am IT guy in team&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Some thoughts for another another startup&lt;/li>
&lt;li>University exams&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>As you can see, I have to be so stuck and busy all the time, but I&amp;rsquo;m not LOL. Just today, I have watched 2 animated movies: Wreck it Ralph 2 &amp;amp; Sing (has veery nice musics in it).&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="full-time-job">Full-time job&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>That full-time job, is such a pain in a**. No, I&amp;rsquo;m not afraid of tasks or smth. It is a bit complicated :(&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-startup-project">A Startup project&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Then we have the first startup. It is a mobile app, built for schools and teacher-student relationships. And actually, it&amp;rsquo;s UI Design is almost complete and I&amp;rsquo;m looking for a mobile developer. You know, in my country, it is not that easy to find one. They are all just coders, coding some e-commerce app over-and-over again. You know, they would do the job, but they need money, and guess what, I don&amp;rsquo;t have that much yet.&lt;br>
Whatever, I&amp;rsquo;m planning of learning flutter myself, but it will take hell a lot of time. Bc I have whole back-end infrastructure on me also Management dashboard, Mobile app, blah blah blah. OK well, we&amp;rsquo;ll see :)&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="another-startup">Another startup&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Ok, that another one, excites my more that others. Unfortunately I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you the details, but that is kinda IoT project of mine. Also the first one.&lt;br>
There are projects which needs a lot of regulation.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="ill-be-right-back-tomorrow-i-hope">&lt;em>I&amp;rsquo;ll be right back tomorrow (I hope)&lt;/em>&lt;/h3></content></item></channel></rss>