<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>weekly on Alvan's Blog</title><link>/tags/weekly/</link><description>Recent content in weekly on Alvan's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 23:10:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/weekly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>🚀 Status Update | 14 Nov 2021</title><link>/posts/2021/status-update-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 23:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2021/status-update-1/</guid><description>⚠️ DISCLAIMER As this is the first one in series, It will be a bit verbose, because I have to do introduction for all ongoing projects. Thanks.
💡 Introduction Hi, fellow reader!
So, recently I was consooming a bit more articles, from other programmers and designers, and suddenly I thought why I&amp;rsquo;m not writing my own thoughts? Basically, this is good idea, for example you get a chance to look back and remember things you have done.</description><content>&lt;h1 id="-disclaimer">⚠️ DISCLAIMER&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>As this is the first one in series, It will be a bit verbose, because I have to do introduction for all ongoing projects. Thanks.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="-introduction">💡 Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Hi, fellow reader!&lt;br>
So, recently I was consooming a bit more articles, from other programmers and designers, and suddenly I thought why I&amp;rsquo;m not writing my own thoughts? Basically, this is good idea, for example you get a chance to look back and remember things you have done. But I was a bit uhmm, how to say, kinda shy. Suddenly, my friend at &lt;a href="https://themisir.com">themisir.com&lt;/a> also said this is a good idea. So, this is me, Alvan, doing it :D&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="-what-is-on-my-mind">💭 What is on my mind?&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Recently my life got a massive DLC and some very interesting things in it. Let&amp;rsquo;s break that into the pieces.&lt;br>
Basically, these are what I am (will be) working with on:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>New remote full-time job&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Education oriented startup (w/brother)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>IoT oriented startup, where I am IT guy in team&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Idea that I&amp;rsquo;m working on&lt;/li>
&lt;li>University exams&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Whole curiosity of learning new cool stuff&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>As you can see, I have to be so stuck and busy all the time, but I&amp;rsquo;m not LOL. Just today, I have watched 2 animated movies: Wreck it Ralph 2 &amp;amp; Sing (has veery nice musics in it).&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="full-time-job">Full-time job&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>That full-time job, is such a pain in a**. No, I&amp;rsquo;m not afraid of tasks or smth. It is a bit complicated :(&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="education-oriented-startup">Education oriented startup&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Then we have the first startup. It is a mobile app, built for schools and teacher-student relationships. And actually, it&amp;rsquo;s UI Design is almost complete and I&amp;rsquo;m looking for a mobile developer. You know, in my country, it is not that easy to find one. They are all just coders, coding some e-commerce app over-and-over again. You know, they would do the job, but they need money, and guess what, I don&amp;rsquo;t have that much yet.&lt;br>
Whatever, I&amp;rsquo;m planning of learning flutter myself, but it will take hell a lot of time. Bc I have whole back-end infrastructure on me also Management dashboard, Mobile app, blah blah blah. OK well, we&amp;rsquo;ll see :)&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="iot-oriented-startup">IoT oriented startup&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Ok, that another one, excites my more that others. Unfortunately I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you the details, but that is kinda IoT project of mine. Also the first one.&lt;br>
There are projects which needs a lot of regulation.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="idea-that-im-working-on">Idea that I&amp;rsquo;m working on&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Oh, this project is a bit interesting and requires attention. It will solve a problem for companies and I&amp;rsquo;m thinking of selling this as an API. But still, this is on very early stage but I have a plan, that hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll follow. Will be writing more on this as project continues.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="learning-new-things">Learning new things&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>For now, I want to learn more about Go.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="-what-i-actually-did-this-week">👷 What I actually did this week?&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>So, interesting question this is. Let&amp;rsquo;s look at the GitHub activity heatmap:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="/images/status-update-1/github-activity-14-11-2021.png" alt="GitHub Activity" title="Github Activity">
&lt;br>
As you can see, last week was a bit non-coding week. Am I happy? Absolutely no! Do I feel guilty? Indeed, yes! Then why the f* I&amp;rsquo;m not doing any work? Well, this is all because of that full-time job. I&amp;rsquo;m drowning in large codebase with no onboarding or whatsoever. I try to understand and use it, but it is slow. Okay, whatever, I&amp;rsquo;ll handle all of these.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Guess what is interesting! UI Design of our startup! I damn like that. This is exactly what makes me excited to work. And I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to write posts about that project&amp;rsquo;s development.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Okay, these was excuses of my laziness. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find exact things that I did this week. But next week won&amp;rsquo;t be like this, I hope :D&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="-what-im-going-to-do-next-week">🎯 What I&amp;rsquo;m going to do next week?&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Do enough research and a bit coding to make first working example of that &lt;a href="#idea-that-im-working-on">idea&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Decide who will work on mobile version of our &lt;a href="#a-startup-project">startup&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Write actual code for this &lt;a href="#a-startup-project">startup&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Wait for other elements to continue working on this &lt;a href="#another-startup">project&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Watch some Disney movies (Idk what are these called. Pixar movies? just movies? Whatever.)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="/images/status-update-1/handshake-gym-programmer.jpg#center" alt="Handshake Meme">&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="-bonus-links">🎁 Bonus links&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>🎶 &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/ZILsHowUjpQ">Amazing music to listen&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h1 id="thanks-very-much-for-bearing-with-me-until-here-3">&lt;strong>Thanks very much for bearing with me until here &amp;lt;3&lt;/strong>&lt;/h1></content></item></channel></rss>